A good health insurance plan
supports you and your family when you
sleep on one bed and it is very important for you to have a
good health insurance plan.
For this we made a video in
which we discussed the top three plans of India
and also saw their ranking on the
other side, how number one is this
Gypsy, number two is Start and number 3
relative video link will be in the description and
i button, that video is almost going to
cross the phase because of your love
and you keep showing love to such remedies, right now
you have many questions in that video, a
lot of details
should be known, that is why I have decided
that on this channel, first of all you will get information about
HDFC Ergo which is India's best
plan, our recording and for that you should know the
details, know its features and one thing
is very important to know and you have many doubts
which I need to solve,
in this video we will cover everything related to ad serials, which was earlier
also called Apollo, its best health
insurance plan,
if
you want then we will also cover Star Sports and
Religare  We will make a video on this.
First and most important thing is for you to
know what are the features of ad serials,
why we kept it number one
in our ranking and also what are such things,
some such features, some such details which
you should not miss. My name is Unanswered
CA CA CS earlier also and welcome all of you
to my channel named Invest
Search for tomorrow. Let's start today's
discussion. Before that, subscribe to this channel
and click the bell icon right now, otherwise it may happen that
some important video gets mixed with you.
Let's start today's discussion on
A
[Music]. First of all, let's
understand that HDFC Ergo,
which was earlier also known as Apollo,
lastly launched a policy above Rs. 10 lakh
in India, which is one of the highest
in the industry. Its death claim
ratio is 10 lakh. You must know
what is Trim Vishu, how much
premium have they collected against that,
how much have they refused to return to the creditors, that is,
in how many classes did they return their
insurance to them?  60% is the ratio of any health
insurance company should be between 50% to
85%,
their 60% which is very good, this is a
good thing here and we will have to note this,
next important thing is first you go to
schools and as Brian joined this Apollo in
Africa, then it has become an even bigger network of
hospitals, its almost a
thousand plus hospitals, today's Vriksha
Gypsy Look plan gives you cashless
treatment, next you
need to know how much you can understand, minimum is relaxed, maximum is
text impression, if we talk about treatment, it
means at a time when more than 35,000
hospitalizations are going to happen, then all your
expenses, whether it is related to ICU, room
rent, medicine
related, diagnostic related, or
options or fans of anything, everything is
covered in this policy, in this policy there is
no room rent for you,
whatever rent you have for this room will be
applicable, free hospital
Expenses like diagnostic
or medical consultation, medicine
and any such expenditure are available to you on the
60th day of free hospitalization.
Post hospitalization,
this
expenditure is available to you on the 1st day after hospitalization. The
point of no claim bonus is
very important for you,
listen to it carefully, it is the most important point.
In every year, your no claim bonus will not be cleared till now.
Your total semester's amount will increase by fifty percent,
meaning if your policy is not cleared for one year, then
instead of 5 lakhs, you will get
7.5 lakhs, if it is not paid for 2 years, then
you will get 10 lakhs. And
your initial semester bonus is of 5 lakhs, but
after paying the no claim bonus, it will give you 10 lakhs.
The maximum can only be doubled, it cannot be doubled.
Meaning, if in August of any 2 years, none of the
first 2 years, then whatever
you had understood in the third year, it will double.
And keep one thing in mind, whenever you  If you plan
anything then it will be
reduced directly, that you will have to understand, the next important thing is the
benefit, what
kind of points are these due to which we had
kept HDFC Ergo at number one, Star at number
two or Rally Ghar at number three, the
most main benefit of HDFC Ergo today is that
its most flexible
is resource management and the best is
what is the second benefit, as soon as
any of your claims comes, you are thwarted hundred percent, I mean,
your basic is always 5 lakhs, your no
claim bonus becomes 10 lakhs by paying it and
you have the illusion of ₹4000 pure silk -
Chawla Chhaila
and you always find it, no, six lakhs, this 5
lakh will be increased and you will understand that 11 lakhs, that is, as much as
your initial understanding is, as soon as
any claim comes, the Muslim will be
thwarted and restored
and this is the best in Gypsy and the
most important point is if you are having any acidity for
which you should take care of your face  If you have taken it for a second,
even in the resort, the
gypsy turns off your game alarm, which is the
most lovely point, that is why
I placed this gypsy at number one. Keeping this point
in mind, the next important
point is the Deccan chargers and day care
process. Whenever you
go to the hospital and get admitted for
less than 24 hours, then it is done in the Deccan. All these
charges are
improved. You will see in your policy document,
from the heart, there is a print documentation
from the country, there is a print department acceptance
section in which you will have
all the details related to this. If you still have any doubt related to
this, we will discuss computers in this video, even
after that, if you have
any doubt in your mind, I have mentioned it
in the description and even the first number, in which it has
a number of the central office of ad serials or
your number, if you have any doubt, then
you should ask them, like you will take a crush investment tomorrow
or mine, then you will get better help
and you will get better service and you will
get a neutral advance and whatever you  Advice will be given
as much as you want, we will go into all the details, we have the
number of the central office, don't
worry you can ask anything without
any confession, without any diet, without
any doubt that I am not providing any wrong information,
all the notes will go to your home.
Next important thing is home
treatment. Now we move on to the next home
treatment. Will the patient get a treatment
plant? It will definitely be available but there will be some
terms and conditions. What will be the conditions
before this? How can it happen that it is
not possible to shift the patient to the hospital or the place where he should be shifted is
not available.
For this, an important point is that if the treatment is more than three days, it
means medical treatment should be given,
that too under the guidance of a medical practitioner. It should
not happen that such treatment is given at home.
This is important, it is free,
tension increases, but post
hospitalization is
not interested in the survey of home treatment. You need to go, there is a
charge for the ambulance. Next
point, you will get ₹2000 for the operation.
Special feature of air ambulance is also included,
but this is only for your own benefit.  It is in the policy
whose total Someshwar Nishit is above 10 lakhs,
maximum up to 2.5 lakhs
is available for 10 lakhs, recording this is available
for air ambulance but it is necessary to have minimum 10 lakhs, will
you get an organ donor, if
someone donates an organ to you then all his
expenses will also be improved, the one who is donating will also get all the
expenses,
but the amount will be
reduced by the amount of your Owaisi policy, health checkup
means whenever you get a
higher mode of health checkup done, you will get it free, let's understand this point
properly, means in the five lucky policy, in this
non-cream of yours,
you can take a refund once after every two years in the
name of health checkup
in the family, if family total is taken
then ₹3 and if individual is taken then
₹2000 and in the policy of 10 lakhs you get every
year which is such in which you do not
press airplane ₹5000 in case of family  And
Dr. can take ₹2000 in the name of health check-up in submarine case,
you people
forget to take referral in the table, in many cases
documentation is required, that whenever
you take a health policy from SD Senior Advocate,
then you always have to take this Irfan,
if any of your insurance is not mentioned in the policy, which
you will get for free, the amount
of insurance will also change, you will have to
see at your basic level what
is your 1.5 balance program from net, if you
remain active, if you download their mobile app, then
you would get some discount
on renewal, you provide all the things and
follow whatever
you give on that too, the next
important point is the maximum age, maximum
84, new issue of policy, sixty-five years,
this has to be kept in mind, but there will be a rain,
after that it can continue till the policy is in force,
how many people can be included in a family floater, after that
maximum six people can be included,
but if properly prepared,
family floater can never be included  In a family suit, the
premium is decided in that family floater
which is linked to the highest premium. Therefore, never
include at least your parents who have more than one child in your family floater. Keep your wife and children
and take insurance from your parents
otherwise your premium will
increase unnecessarily because when these are family
members, one for five people will be
free for four people and it will be decided on the
basis of who has the highest insurance.
If you have parents who have
more than one child, then the premium of the family floater will
increase a lot. So, it is suggested that
you should not include your elderly parents in your policy except one and a half year old parents.
Next important
point is, if I take 2 years premium together, then does it
reduce the premium? Yes
friends, if you take 2 years premium together, then
you get a discount of 7.5 years.
I mean, I suggest that if you have
kept the payment for the second term, you can do it and your financial
condition is good, then you can get 2 years more.  If it is happening then
why not take it,
you should definitely check the list of exclusions once, there are
many
diseases, not just this, there are some things
like STD or HIV or
normal OPD or maternity
charges, these are covered under many policies, so
always check the exclusions,
please West Indies, which is a
3 year thing from you, it is asked many times
and you do not get any shortage of free questions for the first three years,
you need to know, the
next important point comes whether
it is actually the best, Edison had one of the
biggest, Apollo was also very good, like
you have got oil ad with Pepsi, so
its goodness or its network has increased further
and today for investors or
whoever wants to take a policy, my contact
number one is Apollo, number two test and number
three, we will make a video of number two and number three,
if you want, if you want a similar detailed video then
we will make that too, its
last point is the premium,
almost  We live in Africa, it
is very cooperative
based, the premium will be different, meaning
family floater, how many children do you have, if the
child is Rudy, then I will
take it on the basis of the amount, I will get it on my first exam, so it is a better
idea, for example, you have to
take it for ₹5, a person
who is 38 years old, there are two children in his family
and he and his wife, husband, wife
and two children, the maximum age
of the husband is 30 years, family floater should be
₹500, its premium if it is
in Delhi-NCR then it will be almost 1000,
this is the example, now you
can think how PM will do this, if you
need any more information,
you will get the information within 15 minutes, there is a
helpline number in the description, you can connect on it,
you can comment on the helpline number of 1.5 years, and you will
get direct information within 2 minutes, and if you
take it from here, then many distances of many
You get things which will work together for you,
so mix them. If you still have
some doubts, whenever you take a policy, clear all your
doubts and read everything, then read the
article,
any doctor in the description and even faster, I have
given the number in which I can connect.
Do you want me to make a video of Star and Rally Ghar
Ka Paisa, then tell me by commenting.
If you get a lot of requests to do this,
I have almost received mails on the panel to make a
video of HDFC audit, if
you want I will make it in the August four rallies also, then
tell me by commenting that
you want us to
make it all the time, otherwise my coding tips are one of the
best for you, number one today I will
still do this, if you want you can take it from this, we will
meet in the next video, till then you can
investigate and I miss you very soon.
Our serial of options is
going on very interestingly, I am getting a lot of love from you.
If you have not
seen that dish, then watch the option thing cooked on this channel
and subscribe to this channel
without any connection with us on social media.  If you
want to choose on media, keep the link in the description also.
You can add More Than
Seventh House on Telegram. People have already joined, you will definitely join
in the next one. Till then you are in
waiting. If you want our mutual fund or any
financial planning related services, there
is a separate helpline number for that, I have
kept it on the disk, you can do it.